{
    "subject": "Bert_Haanstra",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Fanfare__film_",
    "human_readable": "Bert Haanstra directed the film Fanfare.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9195685982704163,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Bert Haanstra."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490287661552429,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8473523855209351,
            "question": "Who directed the film Fanfare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8126557469367981,
            "question": "Is Bert Haanstra a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666288733482361,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Bert Haanstra's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48916131258010864,
            "question": "What genre is the film Fanfare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48202988505363464,
            "question": "When was the film Fanfare released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37564942240715027,
            "question": "How has Fanfare influenced other filmmakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3437953591346741,
            "question": "What makes the film Fanfare unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08575417101383209,
            "question": "Who are some other filmmakers known for their work in documentaries?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bert Haanstra directed the film Fanfare.",
            "html": "yago_11082_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes the film Fanfare unique?",
            "html": "yago_11082_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Fanfare influenced other filmmakers?",
            "html": "yago_11082_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Fanfare released?",
            "html": "yago_11082_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11082_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Bert Haanstra directed the film Fanfare. Specifically, from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11082/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt:\n\n\"He directed several fiction films.  Fanfare, a comedy situated in a small Dutch village, is still the Netherlands' second most popular film ever (measured at the box office)...\"\n\nFrom file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11082/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt:\n\n\"He directed several fiction films.  Fanfare, a comedy situated in a small Dutch village, is still the Netherlands' second most popular film ever (measured at the box office)...\"\n\nFrom file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11082/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt:\n\n\"He directed several fiction films.  Fanfare, a comedy situated in a small Dutch village, is still the Netherlands' second most popular film ever (measured at the box office)...\"\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Bert Haanstra directed the film Fanfare\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Bert Haanstra directed the film \"Fanfare\" and even give additional details about it, supporting the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}